The Cornwall Pumped Storage Project Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 4. Office Materials, 1965 - 1980; 4; 0.5 Linear Feet Box: 21 - 22
  - Subseries 4.3: Research Materials, 4.3; Box: 22
    - Hudson River Estuary Share Zone: Annotated Natural History Bibliography (Folder 9, Box 22)
    - Land Use Study by the Hudson Highlands Committee of the New York State Council of Parks (oversized) (Folder 10, Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous Maps (oversized) (Folder 11, Box 22)
    - Proposed&Existing Facilities Map (Folder 12, Box 22)
    - Site Plan: Cornwall Pumped Storage Project; Hudson River (Folder 13, Box 22)
    - Statement of Objectives of the Constitutional Council for the Forest Preserve (Folder 14, Box 22)
  - Subseries 4.4: Miscellaneous Office Materials, 4.4; Box: 22
    - Blenheim-Gilboa Pumped Storage Power Project Postcard (Folder 15, Box 22)
    - Button: “Dig they Won’t... Save the Hudson” (Folder 16, Box 22)
    - Comments Upon the Occasion of the 159th Annual Meeting of the Cornwall, New Windsor and Monroe Horse Thief Detecting Society, Oct. 30, 1954 (Folder 17, Box 22)
    - “Consolidated Edison and the Conservationist” Class Project (Folder 18, Box 22)